Conveying Emotions through Shape-changing to Children with and without Visual Impairment
CHI submission
Children explored the skin
and map the shapes to the emotions.
We present five shapes
in both dynamic and static conditions
Dynamic Spikes (Spikes_D)
Static Spikes (Spikes_S)
Dynamic Goosebumps (Goosebumps_D)
Static Goosebumps (Goosebumps_S)
Dynamic Concaves (Concaves_D)
Static Concaves (Concaves_S)
Dynamic Wrinkles (Wrinkles_D)
Static Wrinkles (Wrinkles_S)
Dynamic Tentacles (Tentacles_D)
Static Tentacles (Tentacles_S)
Conveying Emotions through Shape-changing to Children with and without Visual Impairment